rainostream.live 2018-09-30

# Privacy Policy | rainostream.live

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

## How do we protect your information?

  * We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
  * We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.
  * We use regular Malware Scanning.

## We do not use an SSL certificate

We only provide audio visual Content and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers. 

## Do we use cookies?

  * We do not use cookies for tracking purposes
  * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
  * If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
  * However, you will still be able to place orders.

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

## Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Google

Google advertising requirements can be summed up by Googleâ„¢ Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

## We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Googles use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

## We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
  * Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

## COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect childrens privacy and safety online.

## We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

  * Fair Information Practices
  * The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
  * In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify you via email Within 1 business day
  * We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
